https://www.ndareg.com/about/privacy-policy/

Our Commitment To Your PrivacyWe are delighted that you have shown interest in our company by visiting our web site or sharing your contact information with us through other means. If you, like many others, have decided to access some of our electronic services, we may need to process your personal data. When we do this we always make sure that this is in line with current legislation.We’ve put in place many measures to ensure the protection of any data processed through our web site or other electronic channels. As no internet-based transmission is 100% foolproof, you are also free to transfer your personal data via alternative means, such as by phone.Who Are We And Why Do We Need Your Personal Data?NDA Group is a leading drug development consultancy and the premier provider of regulatory, pharmacovigilance and market access advice covering the US and EU market. We work with many of the finest innovative pharmaceutical and biotech companies in the world to help accelerate patient access to important treatments in development.For us to effectively pursue this mission we continually work to extend our network of contacts and colleagues in the industry and to do so we rely on the collection of personal contact details. Our focus is to collect information that allows us to communicate effectively with representatives from our industry, be it to inform and provide intelligence on the current state of the industry or particular parts of it, or to make connections to market and sell our extensive scientific, strategic and operational support to companies that would benefit from them.When we collect personal data, we are considered a Data Controller by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the EU and as such the following contact information is provided:NDA GroupJohanneslundsvägen 2SE-194 61 Upplands VäsbySwedenPhone: +46 (0)8 590 778 00Email: info@ndareg.comWebsite: https://www.ndareg.comFor specific purposes of data processing, please refer to the section “What personal data do we collect and why?”.What Personal Data Do We Collect And Why?General Data And InformationWhen you visit www.ndareg.com or any other web site associated with NDA Group we collect certain information about you and the conditions of your visit. Most of this information is of a more or less general nature, such as what browser or operating system you are using, how you found our web site, what pages you have visited and when your IP-address and what internet service provider you are relying on. We also collect similar data that may be used in the event of attacks on our information system.We collect this data to deliver the content of our website correctly, to optimise the content of our websites as well as advertisement, ensure the long term viability of our IT systems and websites and to provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution of a cyber-attack. We do not use the information to draw conclusions about you.CookiesNDA Group’s websites rely on cookies, text files that store your preferences when browsing our websites. Using cookies we provide you with a user experience tailored to you, such as for instance, allowing our websites to remember who you are so that you do not need to login again each time the website is accessed.You may delete your cookies at any time or turn off the setting of cookies using your web browser. Should you deactivate cookies in your browser, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.Registration On Our WebsiteIt is possible for you to subscribe to certain services on our websites, such as access to intelligence archives or regular newsletters, by providing us with your contact details. Depending on the service, different personal data may be requested and the reason for specific data collection is then specified per type of data.The data you provide here is only used for internal purposes, such as to tailor content displayed on our website to your preferences or to send relevant intelligence and information in areas of your preference directly to you via email.The data may be transferred to a third-party processor, again only for internal purposes, such as newsletter agencies or service providers, to enable the distribution of relevant information to you.When you do signup, certain general information may be registered as well, such as your current IP-address, the date and the time of the registration. This information is only registered with the purpose of preventing misuse of our services and is not passed on to third parties unless there is a statutory obligation to pass on the data or it is required to support a criminal prosecution.Once you’ve signed up on our website you are always entitled to know what information we have stored about you. We are happy to correct or erase any data should you request us to do so. The easiest way to let us know about such a request is to send an email to gdpr@ndareg.com.Contact UsTo request us to get back to you via email or phone we have web forms on our websites and general email addresses that allow you to submit your contact information to NDA Group. This information is automatically stored so we can get back in touch with you promptly.NewslettersNDA Group can keep you updated on current news and intelligence in our industry, as well as on events and offers of NDA Group, on a regular basis via email newsletters (e-shots). Should you register your contact information to receive e-shots, you can rest assured that your personal data will only be used to send e-shots to you.We ask for your consent to send you e-shots. When you give your consent you are always free to revoke it at any time. This is most easily done using the unsubscribe link provided in each e-shot but you may also contact us via other means at any time to revoke your consent.We track the success or failure of our e-shots using standard technology. This means that we may see if and when you opened one of our e-shots and what links you opened. We store and analyse this information to understand what you think is of interest and to continually adapt and improve the information we send you. Should you revoke your consent this data will be deleted from our systems.Web Advertisements And AnalyticsOn our websites, we collaborate with Google to collect and analyse data about browsing behaviour and to support us in presenting relevant ads to you as you browse the web using cookies.The general data necessary to understand this, such as your IP address, is transferred to Google in the United States of America for processing to understand the origin of visitors and clicks to subsequently create commission settlements.Just as with other cookies, they can be blocked and/or deleted from your browser at any time.In addition, it is possible to explicitly opt-out by downloading and installing a browser add-on from https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout that will block any collection of personal data for analytical purposes. The installation of this add-on is computer specific and must be reinstalled should you change computer or reinstall the computer the add-on originally resided on.If you wish to object to the interest-based advertising by Google you can make the desired settings at www.google.de/settings/ads on each computer and browser that you use.How Long Do We Store Your Personal Data?At NDA Group we try to limit the storage of your personal data as much as is possible. This means we will store it only for the time required to fulfil the purpose for which the data was collected and never longer than the statutory retention period unless it is required for us to fulfil additional legal or contractual requirements.
This page uses cookiesOK
